trapcall.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy - TrapCall

### FOR [TRAPCALL.COM](http://trapcall.com/) PHONE SERVICE

Trapcall.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. We take your privacy seriously. You can learn more about our Privacy Policy below. By visiting Trapcall.com or using our services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please choose the most appropriate e-mail address for your message from the list below. We will try to reply as quickly as possible. 

### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This policy covers how Trapcall.com treats personal information that Trapcall.com collects and receives. This includes information related to your past use of Trapcall.com products and services and information about you that is personally identifiable-such as your name, address, email address, or phone number. 

This Privacy Policy, however, does not apply to the practices of companies that are not affiliated with Trapcall.com. 

### What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?

Trapcall.com collects personal information when you register for Trapcall.com services or use Trapcall.com features and products. When you register, we ask for personal information, including but not limited to your name, email address, and zip code. Once you register with Trapcall.com and sign into our services, you are not anonymous to us. Trapcall.com also collects information about your transactions with us, including information about your use of our services. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address and Trapcall.com cookie information. Trapcall.com uses the information for the following purposes, among others: to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve our services, and to contact you. 

### Sharing And/Or Disclosing Information

Information about our customers is an important part of our business. We share customer information only as described below. 

Trapcall.com may disclose customers’ personal information in the following situations: 

  * We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal requirements, or seek to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * We believe it is necessary to disclose such information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to physical safety of any person, or violations of Trapcall.com's Terms of Service. 

In the event Trapcall.com is acquired by or merged with another company, the terms of this Privacy Policy shall continue to apply. In this event, Trapcall.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. Trapcall.com also reserves the right to display targeted advertisements based on personal information. 

### Trapcall.com Cookies

Trapcall.com may set and access Trapcall.com cookies on your computer. We also let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Those cookies are independent of Trapcall.com and are subject to the privacy policies of the company placing the cookie, not to this policy. 

### Your Right To Edit And Delete Your Information

You can contact Trapcall.com to edit or delete your Trapcall.com personal information at anytime if you have terminated your business relationship with us. 

### Children

Trapcall.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell products for purchase by adults, although they may be used by children. If you are under 18, you may use the Trapcall.com website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

### Confidentiality And Security

TrapCall is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information You provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

When you register for TrapCall we ask for information such as your name, email address, billing address, credit card information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card. 

### NOTICE OF CHANGE:

From July 30th, 2015 forward, TrapCall will be cooperating with a third party team trying to identify and eliminate unwanted and potentially illegal robocalls. If this Research & Development (R&D) test is successful, we may in the future offer this service to our subscribers. During the test period, TrapCall will continue to send calls that you reject to your TrapCall voicemail. At the same time, the software installed on our server will be automatically analyzing voicemails to determine whether it is a human or robocall. The service relies on the analysis of the first few seconds of each voicemail to determine whether it is a human or robocall. Recordings of voicemails that are identified as robocalls will be used by the third party team to refine its algorithms and during part of the test period will be forwarded to another third party as part of the R&D effort. In the case of any voicemail that we determine to be left by a robocaller, just the audio recording and the caller ID of the robocaller will be shared with the third party for purposes of R&D. No other personally identifiable information will be shared. IF YOU USE TRAPCALL AFTER JULY 30TH YOU AGREE TO THIS CHANGE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS CHANGE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY, EMAIL US PRIOR TO JULY 30TH AT SUPPPORT@TRAPCALL.COM AND WE WILL MAKE SURE YOUR ACCOUNT IS NOT EFFECTED. 

### Conclusion

Trapcall.com may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about any substantive changes in the way we treat your personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address you specified in your Trapcall.com account application or by placing a notice in a prominent place on our web site. If you have further questions or suggestions regarding Trapcall.com's Privacy Policy, you can contact us at [support@trapcall.com](mailto:support@trapcall.com).
